[
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? We enjoy riding motorcycles. Modern motorcycles are lighter and faster than they was 30 years ago.",
    "answers": ["was"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? My mother was mad at me because I had told her I would be home at 6:00, but I come home at 9:00.",
    "answers": ["come"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? Next year, my family buy a house in Canada. We are going to visit it every summer.",
    "answers": ["buy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? We watched a good movie last night and told our friends about it. Now, they want to see it too. All of us are going to see it again tonight after we are eating dinner.",
    "answers": ["are eating"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? Mary loves to shop, so she left work early today and asked her friend to meet her at the mall. The two of them spending eight hours buying dresses and shoes.",
    "answers": ["spending"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which underlined word has a mistake? The dentist told me that my teeth were healthy, but he want me to go back for a check up soon. I will make another appointment next week when I am free.",
    "answers": ["want"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence is punctuated correctly?",
    "answers": [
      "The children sang and danced.",
      "Tariq and Jordan joined the soccer game and helped the team win.",
      "The test was difficult, but we knew all of the answers.",
      "Michael and Sam gave Paul and me some tips on how to throw a basketball, but they didn't help with our form.",
      "Take a sandwich with you in case you don't have time to stop at a restaurant.",
      "The test was difficult because we didn't have much time to answer all of the questions.",
      "We will buy a new sofa and table if there is a good sale.",
      "Michael and Sam gave Paul and me some tips on how to throw a basketball since we needed some help with our form.",
      "The girls know how to fix cars and play basketball, but the boys don't know how to do those things.",
      "I went to get a loan from the bank; they told me that my credit was good.",
      "You should take a sandwich with you in case you don't have time to stop at a restaurant."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence uses commas correctly?",
    "answers": ["Jane watched a movie, but Steve read a book."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Mary's parents took her to the park, and they invited all of her friends to her birthday party.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? The earthquake was felt 100 miles away; however, it did not wake me up.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? While John was spending his summer working at a difficult job, Mark was enjoying himself at the pool.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? The price of chocolate is going up because it is more difficult to get now.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? The doctor told Mr. Green that he needs to eat more vegetables and get more exercise since his blood pressure is high.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? You want to go out tonight, however, I want to stay home and watch TV.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? We can go to the beach and swim after we have lunch.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Since we don't have much money, we should not plan a big vacation this year.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? When my husband gets home from work we will BBQ some steaks on the grill.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? My brother likes tacos, but my sister does not like them.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Frank bought a new dog and was happy that it didn't bark at night.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Jordan is a happy baby, because his parents play with him all the time.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? You want to go out tonight. I on the other hand want to stay home and watch TV.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? My brother likes tacos, but my sister however does not like them.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? For our vacation we plan to go to California or Washington, but we will wait until summer.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? That was the longest movie that I've ever seen, and I fell asleep about half-way through it.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Mike has three brothers, but one of them, however, does not live in the same city.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? Mrs. Nixon paid her bill, left the restaurant, and went home to take a nap.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? I bought not only a Christmas tree but also lots of presents.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? Jane washed her shirts, shorts, and washed her pants.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? It is true that I loaned you $20 and that you paid me back last week.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? Joe is excited because he got tickets to both the soccer match and the tennis tournament this summer.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are ways to create sentence variety in your writing EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["Avoid using transitions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Good writing uses lots of long sentences to create an academic feel.",
    "answers": ["false"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following punctuated correctly? My mom was mad at me for not cleaning my room. She hadn't told me to clean it, however.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? One way to create sentence variety is to use synonyms and keywords.",
    "answers": ["true"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Grandma can't drive anymore so she takes the bus to go shopping.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following punctuated correctly? You want to go out tonight. I on the other hand want to stay home and watch TV.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You should only worry about sentence variety in the last stages of the writing process, in other words, when you're revising and editing your essay.",
    "answers": ["true"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an essay?",
    "answers": [
      "A piece of writing with multiple paragraphs focused around one topic"
    ]
  },

  {
    "question": "All of the following are rules of academic writing EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": [
      "Use specific pronouns, such as \"I,\" \"me,\" \"we,\" and \"us.\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two required parts of a good thesis statement?",
    "answers": ["Topic and controlling idea"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following should you do in your thesis statement?",
    "answers": ["Write a statement that is not too popular or obvious."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a body paragraph, which of the following sentences has a purpose similar to that of the thesis statement?",
    "answers": ["Topic sentence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words will definitely make a thesis statement arguable?",
    "answers": ["Should"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Supporting ideas are more specific than the topic sentence in a body paragraph.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A good paragraph should have at least two topic sentences.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you create coherence in an essay?",
    "answers": ["Use transitions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The purpose of body paragraphs is to support the thesis statement of an essay?",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An academic essay usually needs 2 body paragraphs to support the thesis statement.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are good transitions to show comparison or contrast EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["Because"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a compare/contrast essay: Bears and lions are both strong animals, but they have different lifestyles.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following statements are true according to this lesson EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": [
      "This lesson taught you that a compare/contrast essay should discuss both similarities and differences.",
      "This lesson taught you that a compare/contrast essay must discuss both similarities and differences."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are good planning activities for a compare/contrast essay EXCEPT what?",
    "answers": ["Writing a second draft"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement for a compare or contrast essay should mention the two things being compared.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement for a compare or contrast essay does not need to indicate if the essay is comparing or contrasting.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a compare/contrast essay: While Michael Jordan was an excellent basketball player, Kobe Bryant is better than Jordan.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A point-by-point comparison essay usually has 2 body paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? In the point-by-point comparison essay, each body paragraph is about one of the two topics the essay is comparing.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a compare/contrast essay: Most new cars have air-conditioning, satellite radio, and rearview cameras.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are good planning activities before you start writing a compare/contrast essay EXCEPT what?",
    "answers": ["Writing a second draft"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay: There are several reasons that ocean water is rising and threatening some islands.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A cause is something that results from something else.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay: There are several reasons that the ocean level is rising and threatening some islands.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An effect is the result of something else.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? This lesson taught you that it's best if a cause/effect essay focuses only on causes or only on effects.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the minimum number of causes you need to write about to make a good cause essay?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The thesis statement in a cause and effect essay must tell the reader what the 3 causes or effects are.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay: The earthquake killed a lot of people near San Francisco.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay needs to tell the reader if the essay will discuss causes or effects.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are important for developing each body paragraph of a cause essay EXCEPT what?",
    "answers": ["A summary of all of the causes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are appropriate transitions to use for a cause or effect essay EXCEPT what?",
    "answers": ["Similarly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? This lesson taught you that a cause/effect essay will focus only on causes or only on effects.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement for an argument essay can be a fact or true statement.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following topics are debatable EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": [
      "Smoking causes cancer and other diseases.",
      "In the '90s, coal and oil were the main sources of energy in the U.S."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? When you write an argument essay, it's important to write equally about both sides of the argument.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? In an argument essay, it's ok if the thesis statement is not arguable because the rest of the essay will develop the argument.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? In an argument essay, answering or responding to opposing view points can help to develop the essay.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following can be used to develop the body paragraphs of an argument essay EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["Explaining all of the opposing views in detail"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Giving money to beggars on the street does not encourage them to get a job.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Eating a lot of greasy food causes weight gain and other health problems.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words most closely means the same thing as \"argument\" when we are talking about an argument essay?",
    "answers": ["Persuasion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a good way to make your academic essays longer?",
    "answers": [
      "Use some different types of paragraphs to add more body paragraphs."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Argument essays should have at least how many reasons to support the argument?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence below has a correctly formatted quotation (using MLA format)? (Be sure to check the punctuation carefully.)",
    "answers": [
      "He explains that they “edit and re-edit digital messages as much as they like\nuntil they decide they’ve perfectly conveyed their thoughts” (Ghuman)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence below has a correctly formatted quotation (using MLA format)? (Be sure to check the punctuation carefully. Where should the period go?)",
    "answers": [
      "There is more for Samsung to worry about because it \"has been facing stiff competition for its premium smartphones from rival Apple” (Becker)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are types of paragraphs (modes of discourse) that you can use to help develop an argument essay?",
    "answers": ["description, argument, compare/contrast, narrative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of body paragraph is this?",
    "answers": ["description"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are features of an advanced argument essay? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "It uses a variety of paragraph types to develop the argument.",
      "It uses outside sources to support the argument."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you have to remember to do when you use an outside source in your academic essays? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Cite the source.",
      "Use correct formatting, such as MLA.",
      "Use quotation marks if copying words.",
      "Integrate or blend the quoted words with your own words."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the original source on the left and the student's writing on the right and decide if the student plagiarized or not.",
    "answers": ["No, there is not plagiarism."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? It's ok to borrow some ideas from an outside source as long as you don't copy the exact words in your own essay.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can happen if a student is caught plagiarizing in an American college? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The student can fail the assignment.",
      "The student can be kicked out of the school",
      "The student can fail the class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does synthesis mean in a synthesis essay?",
    "answers": ["to blend"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are sources used for in a synthesis essay?",
    "answers": ["They help to support the writer's ideas."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? It was not surprising to many people that a judge decided that Robin Thicke had \"noticeably ripped off Marvin Gaye's 1977 hit 'Got to Give It Up' when he wrote the smash hit 'Blurred Lines' with Pharrell Williams and T.I.\" (Grow).",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? Roger Friedman explains that Mariah Carey has been in this situation before and because the \"work tapes and notebooks of writing sessions have haunted Carey in other plagiarism cases,\" this case does not look good for her.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? While plagiarism has always existed, the problem is that young people are \"representative of a different generation, one that freely mixes and matches from the whirring flood of information across new and old media, to create something new\" (Kulish).",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? Nicholas Kulish reports that \"the controversy did not appear to be hurting book sales\" as it was \"ninth over all among books on the German Amazon site.\"",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? There have been several similar cases of plagiarism at the University of Virginia, but there has been \"no consistency in the way plagiarism events are handled\" at that school (\"UVa Expels\").",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? Luckily, \"the controversy did not appear to be hurting book sales. On Thursday afternoon 'Axolotl Roadkill' was ninth over all among books on the German Amazon site, albeit with many nasty postings about the plagiarism controversy.\" (Kulish).",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? For example, \"Robin Thicke noticeably ripped off Marvin Gaye's 1977 hit 'Got to Give It Up' when he wrote the smash hit 'Blurred Lines' with Pharrell Williams and T.I. (Grow).",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? However, they are a \"representative of a different generation, one that freely mixes and matches from the whirring flood of information across new and old media, to create something new\" (Kulish).",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A documented essay can be written without using any sources.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A Works Cited entry usually starts with an author's last name.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A parenthetical in-text citation should always use the author's last name.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A documented essay is usually an illustration or an argument essay.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Sources are used in documented essays to make or introduce important points in the essay.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Academic essays should have only 5 paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You should use a variety of types of body paragraphs in a documented essay.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you integrate a quote well?",
    "answers": [
      "Use only the important part of the quote and blend it with my own words."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? For academic research, you should write complete sentences when you take notes on an article.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Most school library webpages have databases that anyone is free to use as long as they have an Internet connection.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the most academic kind of source?",
    "answers": ["library databases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of an annotated bibliography?",
    "answers": ["to help you summarize and evaluate your sources"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You must always use a formal outline to plan an effective research paper.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would be the most effective thesis statement for a research paper?",
    "answers": [
      "The U.S. government should require that all companies pay men and women the same amount of money for equal work."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An annotated bibliography for a college class is always written in MLA format.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phrase appropriate for an academic essay? drunk as a skunk",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? gonna",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? y'all",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? increase",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You should use as many academic words as possible in your research paper even if you don't know what all of them mean.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a reason to use a statistic in your research paper?",
    "answers": ["to make your paper longer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not an appropriate place to use a statistic in your research paper?",
    "answers": ["in the thesis statement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following groups of words is definitely not on the Academic Word List?",
    "answers": [
      "snooze, nerdy, lame",
      "trashy, know-it-all, grouchy",
      "crash, cop, messy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? therefore",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? dummy",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phrase appropriate for an academic essay? in his article",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this expression appropriate for an academic essay? It's a piece of cake.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Search engines like Google.com and Yahoo.com are the best places to do all your academic research.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following internet sites would be acceptable to use when searching for sources for a research paper?",
    "answers": ["scholar.google.com"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a good search term for this topic: Topic: the economy",
    "answers": ["financial crisis of 2008"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, where is the best place to look for sources for a research paper?",
    "answers": ["library databases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are questions to ask when determining reliability of a a source EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["How long is the source?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first thing to do after you receive a research paper assignment?",
    "answers": ["Think of a research question."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Most research papers share all of the following characteristics EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["They are worth 150 pts."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Every research assignment you will be assigned in college will have different requirements.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is EasyBib?",
    "answers": [
      "It's a website that helps students format their Works Cited page or References list."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? If you paste a link to your online source in the EasyBib website, EasyBib will always supply all of the information you need to format your Works Cited entry.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Works Cited Page: Other Common Sources tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 8th ed., which kind of source is this?",
    "answers": ["recorded television episode"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Abbreviations tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 9th ed. what is the correct way to write the month, January, in the publication date for a journal in a Works Cited page?",
    "answers": ["Jan."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click any tab you need to to answer the question below about this sample Works Cited page shown. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) In this Works Cited page using MLA 9th ed., which kinds of sources are A, B, and C? Choose the answer below that identifies all three sources correctly.",
    "answers": [
      "A. article with an author from an electronic source\n\nB. article with no author from an electronic source\n\nC. printed book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Abbreviations tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) True or False? According to MLA 9th ed., you should write the complete publisher's name for a book in your Works Cited page, but it's all right to omit words like \"Inc.\" or \"Corp.\"",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct verb to fill in the blank below. She bought a house and then __________ that it needed a lot of repairs.",
    "answers": ["discovered"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct verb to fill in the blank below. My mom likes to watch TV. She _________ asleep in her chair watching TV every night.",
    "answers": ["falls"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct verb to fill in the blank below. She didn't come to our party. She said she ________ an invitation.",
    "answers": ["hadn't received"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct verb to fill in the blank below. Walter has seen that movie five times. He says it just makes him feel good, so I was not surprised to see that he _________ the movie again last night.",
    "answers": ["watched"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence is a compound sentence?",
    "answers": [
      "Ross lives in New Jersey, and he works in New York City.",
      "Lions are kings of the jungle, so everyone respects them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this sentence need a comma? The mailman came to our house but he didn't bring any mail for me.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the sentence that is punctuated correctly.",
    "answers": [
      "Mom asked my brother and me to help her cook dinner, but we weren't much help."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence is NOT punctuated correctly.",
    "answers": ["My car got a flat tire on the freeway I was late to work."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of sentence is this? The captain of the airplane told us to buckle our seat-belts, so we did.",
    "answers": ["compound"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of sentence is this? The scientists are concerned about the rising temperatures on the planet but don't know what to do about it.",
    "answers": ["simple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? I want to buy an airplane ticket to visit my family because I have not seen them in a long time.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? I don't know if I can go to the movie with you after we get home from school.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? While I was driving home from work yesterday, I saw an accident on the freeway.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? Since you are my best friend I want you to come to my birthday party in Hawaii.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? I like a pizza with mushrooms, onions, and peppers on it, but my husband likes a pizza with only cheese on it.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? The photo, which I took, is of a horse running in a field.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? In the afternoon we can go to the beach and swim.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a parallel structure? Amy is interested in neither what you say nor what you do.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a parallel structure? Bill is interested in not only psychology but also in how plants grow.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? You can go outside and play, but you need to come back when it's dark.",
    "answers": ["yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence a parallel structure? My 4-year old daughter is very smart, pretty, and knows how to use a computer.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a way to create sentence variety?",
    "answers": [
      "Write a lot of long sentences.",
      "Make sure all your sentences are very long."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When should you think about putting sentence variety in your essays?",
    "answers": ["When you are revising your essay."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this student's paragraph use good sentence variety? My homestay is beautiful. The back yard is natural and green. There is a light green table. It has flowers in the middle. The inside of the house has a modern living room. There is a television hanging on the wall. There are three speakers on the ceiling which make you feel you are in the theater. The comfortable kitchen is located next to the livingroom. The kitchen has a really nice shape. It looks like a restaurant’s kitchen. My organized room is quiet and is located in front of the stairs. In all, my homestay’s house looks nice.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are effective ways to write an introductory paragraph for an essay EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["Explain several reasons to support your thesis statement."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two parts of a good thesis statement? Choose two answers.",
    "answers": ["Topic", "Controlling idea"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The purpose of body paragraphs is to support the thesis statement of an essay.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the minimum number of body paragraphs usually needed in an academic essay to support the thesis statement?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay: Cell phone prices have gotten cheaper, and this has helped a lot of consumers.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a good tool for planning a cause or effect essay?",
    "answers": ["Two circles"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Borrowing money to buy a new house is a big decision.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? People should not be forced by the government to vaccinate their children.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Temperatures are getting hotter and rain is badly needed.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Children should not be expected to do homework in elementary school.",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To avoid plagiarism, which of the following should you do? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Cite the source either in an attribution or in parentheses at the end of the sentence.",
      "Put quotation marks around words that I copy exactly from the source.",
      "Use quotations on all borrowed phrases and sentences.",
      "Cite the source for any borrowed words or ideas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Citing sources any time you borrow words or ideas from an outside source will help you avoid trouble in American universities.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which citation format are you learning to use in this course?",
    "answers": ["MLA (Modern Language Association)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Purdue Owl?",
    "answers": [
      "It is a website with information to guide students in formatting their essays in MLA or APA format."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use this link to the Purdue Owl's MLA page to help you answer the following question. You will have to click on one of the tabs on the left menu of the webpage to find information on the Formatting and Style Guide. Purdue Owl MLA Which of the following is optional in MLA formatting?",
    "answers": ["date of access"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key to choosing good search terms?",
    "answers": ["think of several specific phrases to search"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for a more specific topic under the following general topic: urban development",
    "answers": ["smoking rules in public housing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: crime",
    "answers": ["auto-theft statistics in Chicago"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: national security",
    "answers": ["visa screening policies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an annotated bibliography?",
    "answers": [
      "It is a list of articles related to your topic, and it summarizes and evaluates these."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Most research papers are about 5 pages long.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement is optional in your research paper.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Creating an outline, either formal or informal, can help you organize your ideas so that you write a more logical research paper.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement must have a topic and controlling idea.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An outline must include Roman numerals and capital and lowercase letters to keep it organized.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were using EasyBib to help you create a Works Cited entry for an electronic news source, and EasyBib gave you the results below, what additional information would you have to provide in order to create the citation?",
    "answers": ["article title, author, and publisher"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this sentence need a comma? Wilson watched the football game on TV but wished to be at the game.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? It's OK to borrow some ideas from an outside source without citing it as long as you don't copy the exact words in your own essay.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? Roger Friedman says, \"Carey has several other blots on her record in the songwriting department, including lifting the music from Maurice White's famous hit by the Emotions, called \"Best of My Love.\"",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, why should you take notes during your research?",
    "answers": ["so you can organize your research"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following quote well-integrated, or blended with the writer's own words? The University of Virginia honor code clearly states its rules and \"requires students to pledge not to cheat, lie or steal, or tolerate those who do\" (\"UVa Expels\").",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Every research paper must have at least one statistic to make the essay effective.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are important to do in your writing to make your research paper academic and effective EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["Avoid specific examples in your writing."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Statistics can be used to start body paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Statistics should not be used to start or end your body paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? It is ok to use contractions like \"can't\" and \"won't\" in your research paper so that you have more space on the pages to write about important ideas in your essay.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? EasyBib is free to use for formatting in MLA and APA.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were using EasyBib to help you create a Works Cited entry for a YouTube video, and EasyBib gave you the results below, what additional information would you have to provide in order to create the citation?",
    "answers": ["the author of the video and publication date"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? EasyBib always creates a correctly formatted Works Cited entry when you give it the correct information.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a very good search term for this topic? Topic: Gun Laws",
    "answers": ["guns"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: workplace ethics",
    "answers": ["paid paternity leave for new fathers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use this link to the Purdue Owl's MLA page to help you answer the following question. You will have to click on one of the tabs on the left menu of the webpage to find information about in-text citations. Purdue Owl MLA Which of the following does not use a correct MLA citation?",
    "answers": [
      "Romantic poetry is characterized by the \"spontaneous overflow of powerful feelings\" (Wordsworth, 1800, p. 263)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the appropriate tab on the left to answer questions about creating a Works Cited page for book sources. Purdue OWL MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 9th ed., which of the following is not a correctly formatted Works Cited entry for a book?",
    "answers": ["Option:"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a good number of body paragraphs for most kinds of academic essays?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this an effective thesis statement for an argument essay? Temperatures are getting hotter and rainfall has been less than the historical average.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The following is a good thesis statement for a compare/contrast essay: PC and Mac computers both have strengths; however, Mac has some advantages over PC.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A compare/contrast essay usually compares three or more things, people, or ideas.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a cause/effect essay: The fact that cell phone prices have gotten cheaper over the years has helped consumers in many ways.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following is a good thesis statement for a compare/contrast essay: Superman and Batman are the super heroes in several popular movies.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a parallel structure? Bill is interested not only in psychology but also in becoming an actor.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following sentence punctuated correctly? For Mary's birthday her parents took her to the park, and they invited all of her friends.",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Most research assignments tell you the exact topic you should write about.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  }
]
